<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_description">Navigate home</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_up_description">Navigate up</string>
    <string name="abc_action_menu_overflow_description">More options</string>
    <string name="abc_action_mode_done">Done</string>
    <string name="abc_activity_chooser_view_see_all">See all</string>
    <string name="abc_activitychooserview_choose_application">Choose an app</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_off">OFF</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_on">ON</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_alt_shortcut_label">Alt+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_ctrl_shortcut_label">Ctrl+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_delete_shortcut_label">delete</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_enter_shortcut_label">enter</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_function_shortcut_label">Function+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_meta_shortcut_label">Meta+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_shift_shortcut_label">Shift+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_space_shortcut_label">space</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_sym_shortcut_label">Sym+</string>
    <string name="abc_prepend_shortcut_label">Menu+</string>
    <string name="abc_search_hint">Search…</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_clear">Clear query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_query">Search query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_search">Search</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_submit">Submit query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_voice">Voice search</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with">Share with</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with_application">Share with %s</string>
    <string name="abc_toolbar_collapse_description">Collapse</string>
    <string name="about_miui_auto_discovery_subtitle">When allowed, system will prompt nearby Mi Home devices to be connected</string>
    <string name="account_error_msg">Make sure %s account is the same as your current Mi Home account and try again</string>
    <string name="account_mi_home">Mi Home</string>
    <string name="app_name">Mi Home</string>
    <string name="app_name2">Mi Home</string>
    <string name="auth_finish_dialog_stay_in_mijia">Stay in Mi Home</string>
    <string name="auth_no_match">Current app and Mi Home are not signed in to the same region, or the device is not paired with this account</string>
    <string name="camera_page_title">Mi Home camera</string>
    <string name="check_account_retry">To authorize, switch to the same account as Mi Home app first</string>
    <string name="client_manage">Mi Home</string>
    <string name="comment_for_mihome_title">Rate Mi Home</string>
    <string name="connect_success_dialog_message">Newly added devices are available on Smart Household Device tap or in Mi Home App</string>
    <string name="count_down_end">Event starts</string>
    <string name="count_down_end_in">Ends in</string>
    <string name="count_down_pre">Starts at %1$s %2$s,%3$s</string>
    <string name="count_down_start">Countdown</string>
    <string name="count_down_txt">Count Down</string>
    <string name="cs_default_deivce_name">Mi Home Smart Camera</string>
    <string name="dialog_auto_start_msg1">Allow Mi Home app to run when device is on, in order to use the following features normally:</string>
    <string name="dialog_auto_start_msg6">Run Mi Home app when device is on?</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_force_update">Current Mi Home version is too old, maybe you can\'t\10use some features normally. Update to the latest version\10to have more fun.</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_half_force_update">Latest Mi Home app version %s is available,\10update now?</string>
    <string name="disclaim_content">To use our service, you need to read and agree to Mi Home\'s #start#User Agreememnt and Privacy Policy#end#.\10To ensure it can function normally, Mi Home might need to acquire your network, location, the authorization to turn on your Bluetooth, use your cellular network and microphone. Do you confirm?</string>
    <string name="disclaim_join_user_exp_plan4">Please agree to the following statements in order to use Mi Home. You have read and agree to the following content.</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_fastforward_description">Fast-forward</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_fullscreen_description">Full-screen mode</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_next_description">Next track</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_pause_description">Pause</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_play_description">Play</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_previous_description">Previous track</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_repeat_all_description">Repeat all</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_repeat_off_description">Repeat none</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_repeat_one_description">Repeat one</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_rewind_description">Rewind</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_shuffle_description">Shuffle</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_stop_description">Stop</string>
    <string name="exo_download_completed">Download completed</string>
    <string name="exo_download_description">Download</string>
    <string name="exo_download_downloading">Downloading</string>
    <string name="exo_download_failed">Download failed</string>
    <string name="exo_download_notification_channel_name">Downloads</string>
    <string name="exo_download_removing">Removing downloads</string>
    <string name="exo_item_list">%1$s, %2$s</string>
    <string name="exo_track_bitrate">%1$.2f Mbps</string>
    <string name="exo_track_mono">Mono</string>
    <string name="exo_track_resolution">%1$d × %2$d</string>
    <string name="exo_track_selection_auto">Auto</string>
    <string name="exo_track_selection_none">None</string>
    <string name="exo_track_selection_title_audio">Audio</string>
    <string name="exo_track_selection_title_text">Text</string>
    <string name="exo_track_selection_title_video">Video</string>
    <string name="exo_track_stereo">Stereo</string>
    <string name="exo_track_surround">Surround sound</string>
    <string name="exo_track_surround_5_point_1">5.1 surround sound</string>
    <string name="exo_track_surround_7_point_1">7.1 surround sound</string>
    <string name="exo_track_unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="family_invite_msg_title">Mi Home group invitation</string>
    <string name="feedback_app_experience">Mi Home app</string>
    <string name="find_device_tips">System will prompt nearby Mi Home devices to be connected. Turn off in Mi Home-Profile-Settings</string>
    <string name="go_to_login_mes">To use voice control, sign in to Mi Home first</string>
    <string name="group_type_webinfo">Mi Home Forum</string>
    <string name="location_disable_hint">Allow Mi Home to obtain location information in order to scan for nearby devices</string>
    <string name="lock_empty_message_need_login">Tap to sign in to Mi Home</string>
    <string name="lock_login_tip">Sign in to Mi Home</string>
    <string name="login_des_tips">You didn\'t sign in. Tap to sign in and experience Mi Home</string>
    <string name="mesh_gateway_desc">Bluetooth Mesh gateway: all Mi Home Bluetooth devices added to the same account can connect to the Internet through this device, and can also remotely view and control it.</string>
    <string name="mi_home_content">Experience the latest of Mi - from smart phones to smart devices, exclusively at Mi Home</string>
    <string name="mi_home_product3_content">We currently support the following payment options at Mi Home and are constantly working towards adding more options for a convenient shopping experience:\101.Credit Card\102.Debit Card\103.Cash.</string>
    <string name="mi_home_title">Mi Home - Retail Experience Store</string>
    <string name="mi_smart_home_cs">Mi Home customer service</string>
    <string name="miio_ble_gateway_scan_empty">No Mi Home Bluetooth devices were found near the gateway,</string>
    <string name="miio_ble_gateway_scan_empty_international">No Mi Home Bluetooth devices were found near the gateway</string>
    <string name="miio_setting_info_wx">Follow Mi Home Official Account</string>
    <string name="mijia_auth">Mi Home authorization</string>
    <string name="mikey_family_union">Mi Home devices automation</string>
    <string name="mini_program_tip">How to use Mi Home mini program?</string>
    <string name="miui_earphone_unsupport_server">The region in your Mi Home needs to be changed to Mainland China in order to pair to this device.</string>
    <string name="noti_token_expired_title">Mi Home</string>
    <string name="open_device_account_erro">Mi Home accounts don\'t match, switch accounts?</string>
    <string name="open_find_device_tips">When turned on, system will prompt nearby Mi Home devices to be connected. Turn on/off in Mi Home-Profile-Settings</string>
    <string name="open_location_permission">Allow Mi Home to access your location to search for networks nearby</string>
    <string name="scene_user_license_content">In the event of any of the following circumstances, Mi Home won\'t assume any legal liabilities\10 1. Anyone creating automation tasks in any way will be regarded as having voluntarily accepted this disclaimer.\10 2. This function is still in a pilot phase and is provided only for the purposes of experience and communication. Any problems that may arise in use of the app will gradually be corrected in the updated versions.\10 3. If automation tasks fail to run or run improperly due to reasons including, but not limited to, attacks by hackers, network disconnections, network delays or devices going offline, we won\'t assume any responsibilities but will try our best to reduce losses or consequences caused for the users as a result.\10 4. In the case of any losses incurred by improper use, we will not assume any legal liability.\10\10</string>
    <string name="search_menu_title">Search</string>
    <string name="server_change_server_message_no_login">For data protection purposes, products of different regions can only be accessed from their respective data center. Switching server may affect Mi Home and its products. Are you sure to switch？</string>
    <string name="share_score_score_info">Share my Smart index from Mi Home</string>
    <string name="share_wx_mini_title">Have fun with Mi Home smart devices</string>
    <string name="smart_config_manual_text">Connect your phone to \"%s\" and return to Mi Home app</string>
    <string name="smart_config_mijia_camera_zhilian">Mi Home Security Camera (Hotspot Direct)</string>
    <string name="smart_life_tips2">Simplify your life with Mi Home smart devices</string>
    <string name="smartgroup_share_title">Mi Home data</string>
    <string name="smarthome_device_mijia">Add to Mi Home</string>
    <string name="smarthome_launcher_downloading_app">Downloading Mi Home app…</string>
    <string name="splash_copy_right">Copyright 2014–2016 © By Mi Home</string>
    <string name="status_bar_notification_info_overflow">999+</string>
    <string name="stay_in_mihome">Stay in Mi Home</string>
    <string name="tag_transfer_welcome">Explore more with rooms in Mi Home</string>
    <string name="user_license_btn_text">User Agreement &amp; Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="user_license_title">Mi Home User Agreement &amp; Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="user_privacy_new">Our rivacy policy was updated on the 20th of October, 2017. We have revised our Privacy Policy, and from this date onwards this policy can provide details about how we manage the personal information you disclose when using any Mi Home products or services, with the exception of certain Mi Home products or services that provide their own independent Privacy Policy.&lt;br/&gt; Please take some time to become familiar with our privacy practices, and please let us know if you have any questions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Our promise to you&lt;br/&gt; This Privacy Policy sets out how Xiaomi and its affiliates (hereafter Xiaomi or We) collect, use, disclose, process and protect the information you provide through the Mi Home app when using our products and services. If we ask you to provide certain information to verify your identity when using Mi Home products and services, we will use this information strictly in accordance with this policy and/or our user terms and conditions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; This policy is formulated with your needs in mind; it is important that you fully understand our personal data collection and usage practices and that you are ultimately in control of the personal information you provide. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; In this Privacy Policy, personal information refers to the information itself or other information accessible to Xiaomi that allows us to identify the data of specific individuals. Such personal information includes your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; By using Mi Home products and services, you acknowledge that you have read, acknowledged, and accepted all the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy, including any changes we may make at any time. We are committed to protecting the privacy, confidentiality and security of your personal information in accordance with applicable laws (including the data protection laws specific to your location). At the same time we promise our staff and agents will fulfill these obligations. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Finally, what we want is the best experience for our users. If you have any questions about the data processing practices outlined in this Privacy Policy, please contact our Data Protection Officer at privacy@xiaomi.com so that we can handle your special needs. We are happy to deal with your problem directly. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; What information is collected and how is it used? &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; The types of information collected&lt;br/&gt; We will ask you to provide the personal information necessary to provide you with our services. If you do not provide this personal information, we may not be able to provide you with our products or services. &lt;br/&gt; We collect the following types of information (whether or not they are personal information): &lt;br/&gt; • Information you provide or upload to us: We may collect any or all of the personal information you provide to us, such as your name, phone number, e-mail address, Mi Account information (such as your security-related information, name, birthday, or gender), information or data that your access to the Mi Home platform synchronizes, the account and related settings created on the Mi Home platform, the device you added or messages you sent, feedback, and any other information you provide to us. &lt;br/&gt; • Information related to your handheld terminal or SIM card: Information related to running the Mi Home handheld terminal. For example, the IMEI number, IMSI number, system version, device manufacturer information, model name, and network operator. &lt;br/&gt; • Device information: Device information associated with your account. For example, MAC address, DID, and information collected by the corresponding device sensors (such as temperature, humidity, PM2.5, AQI, TDS, tVOC, CO2, ambient light, smoke concentration, natural gas concentration, power consumption, operating trajectory, signal strength, action/screen detection, body temperature, body weight, and on/off status), as well as the operating conditions of device consumables (such as the filter, filter service life, etc.). &lt;br/&gt; • Information we specify about you: We may collect and use information such as your Mi Account. &lt;br/&gt; • Location information (specific services/features only): Various types of information related to your location. For example, country code, city code, mobile network code, cell ID, latitude and longitude information, and language settings. &lt;br/&gt; • Login information: Information related to your use of certain features and devices. Examples include cookies and other anonymous identifier technologies, IP addresses, temporary message history, and standard system logs. &lt;br/&gt; • Additional information: Environmental characteristic value or ECV (device-bound account (e-mail and phone number), connected Wi-Fi account and password, geo-location information, etc.) &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; We may also collect other types of anonymous information that are not associated with individuals. For example, it is possible to collect the device model and firmware version number of the device used to access Mi Home when using a particular service. The purpose of collecting such information is to improve the services we provide you. The type and amount of information collected depends on how you use, join, or participate in our products and/or services. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; How this personal information will be used&lt;br/&gt; The purpose of collecting personal information is to provide you with products and/or services and to ensure that we comply with applicable laws. You hereby agree that we process personal information for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy and disclose personal information to our affiliates (which cover communications, social media, technology and cloud businesses) and third-party service providers (as defined below). &lt;br/&gt; We may use your personal information for the following purposes: &lt;br/&gt; • Providing, processing, maintaining, improving, and developing the products and/or services we provide to you, as well as through devices or Mi Home-provided services. &lt;br/&gt; • Communicating with you about your devices, services, or any general inquiries such as updates, device firmware/software upgrades, customer advisory support, related information, notifications, and more. &lt;br/&gt; • Analyzing and developing statistical information related to the use of our products and services to better improve them. &lt;br/&gt; • Store and maintain information about you for our business operations or legal obligations. &lt;br/&gt; Here\'s more details on how we use your information, which may include personal information. &lt;br/&gt; • Creating your account. The personal information collected when creating an account on a mobile device is used to create a user\'s personal account and profile page. &lt;br/&gt; • Providing location-based services. We may use location information to provide you with the best possible user experience when using Mi Home and accessing Mi Home devices, such as analyzing and providing information about the surrounding weather, air quality, water quality, and launching the appropriate devices and experiences in advance according to your choices. You can turn this feature off at any time by entering device settings or stopping your use of this application. access. &lt;br/&gt; • Device access. In order to access Mi Home, your device must connect to the network. Therefore, when adding devices to the Mi Home app, you need to enter the corresponding Wi-Fi name and password. This information is only used for the device distribution network. We will encrypt the Wi-Fi and password data you input and store it in your mobile terminal; we will not upload it to the server, you can enter the device to delete the information at any time. &lt;br/&gt; • Device status display. Status information (such as temperature, humidity, PM2.5, AQI, TDS, tVOC, CO2, ambient light, smoke concentration, natural gas concentration, power consumption, operating trajectory, signal strength, action/screen detection, body temperature, body weight, and on/off status), as well as the operating conditions of device consumables (such as the filter, filter service life, etc.) allow you to remotely view the status of your device so you can see how well it is running in your home at any time. &lt;br/&gt; • Setting up automated tasks. Event information reported by your device (such as temperature, humidity, PM2.5, AQI, TDS, tVOC, CO2, ambient light, smoke concentration, natural gas concentration, power consumption, operating trajectory, signal strength, and action/screen detection) can be used to create your own personal automated tasks, such as accessing Mi Home’s temperature sensor when the temperature is higher than 30℃ to access control of Mi Home’s smart air conditioner to start cooling. &lt;br/&gt; • Providing push services. The account and IMEI number will also be used to provide Mi Home push services to send notifications to users. You can turn this feature off at any time by changing your preferences under Message Settings. &lt;br/&gt; • Verifying user identity. Mi Home uses ECV values to verify user identities and ensure that hackers or unauthorized persons cannot log in. &lt;br/&gt; • Collecting user feedback. The feedback you choose to provide is extremely valuable to helping Mi Home improve our services. In order to follow the feedback you choose to provide, Mi Home may use the personal information you provide to contact you and to keep records. &lt;br/&gt; • Sending notifications. From time to time we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as unexpected device health notifications, customized device push notifications (such as motion detection alerts, cleanups, etc.), or changes to our terms and conditions or policies. &lt;br/&gt; • Direct marketing. We may use your name, phone number, email address, Mi and Mi Home accounts, and IMEI numbers to provide you with promotional materials for products and services from Xiaomi and our partners (providing web, mobile applications, and cloud products and services). To provide a better user experience, we recommend these products, services, and events based on your purchase history, site browsing history, birthday, age, gender, and location. We strictly adhere to the data protection laws of your location and require independent, express permission, so we will only use your personal information with your consent or your lack of objection. You have the right to terminate our use of personal data intended for direct marketing. If you no longer wish to receive certain categories of e-mail, you can unsubscribe using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each e-mail. We will not send your personal information to our business partners for direct marketing. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; With whom do we share your information? &lt;br/&gt; We will not sell your personal information to a third party. &lt;br/&gt; From time to time, we may disclose your personal information to third parties (as defined below) to provide the products or services you request. We may disclose information to third-party service providers and affiliates listed below in this section. In the circumstances described in this section, you can rest assured that Xiaomi will only share your personal information based on your authorization. You understand that Xiaomi will comply with applicable local data protection laws through contractual third-party practices and obligations when Xiaomi shares your personal information with third-party service providers under any of the circumstances described below. Xiaomi will contract to ensure that third-party service providers comply with the privacy standards applicable to them in your jurisdiction. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Sharing information within our group and with third party service providers&lt;br/&gt; In order to successfully conduct business and provide you with the full functionality of our products and services, we may from time to time disclose your personal information to other Xiaomi affiliates (dealing with communications, social media, technology or cloud businesses) or our third party service providers (our mailing houses, delivery service providers, telecommunications companies, data centers, data storage facilities, customer service providers, advertising and promotion service providers, and agents representing Xiaomi) [Affiliates and/or other third parties] (collectively third party service providers). Such third party service providers may handle your personal information on behalf of Xiaomi or for one or more of the above items. When using certain mobile applications on our devices, we may share your IP address with third parties in order to provide you with certain services you request. If you no longer wish to allow us to share this information, please contact us at privacy@xiaomi.com. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Sharing information with the Xiaomi Ecosystem Company&lt;br/&gt; Xiaomi works together with a group of other cool companies to form the Mi Ecosystem. A Mi Ecosystem company is an independent entity invested and operated by Xiaomi and is an expert in these fields. Xiaomi may disclose your personal information to a Mi Ecosystem company in order to provide and improve exciting products and services (including software and hardware) from the Mi Ecosystem. Some products and services still use the Xiaomi/Mi Home brands, but others may use their own brands. From time to time, the Mi Ecosystem may share data related to Xiaomi/Mi Home brand products and services in order to provide software and hardware services for better functionality and user experience. If Xiaomi is involved in the acquisition, merger, acquisition or disposal of all or any part of its assets, we will notify by email and/or prominently on our website of any changes to the ownership of your personal information or its use, as well as any options you may have regarding your personal information. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Sharing information with others&lt;br/&gt; Mi Home may disclose your personal information without further consent, as required by applicable law. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Information that does not require consent&lt;br/&gt; • We may share anonymous information with third parties (such as advertisers on our website) in an aggregated form for commercial purposes; we may share general usage trends for our services, such as the number of customers in certain groups who buy certain products or engage in certain transactions. &lt;br/&gt; • In order to avoid doubt, Xiaomi may collect, use or disclose your personal information, without your consent, in the circumstances and to the extent expressly permitted by the Law on Local Data Protection (for example, in order to comply with a summons), and we may disclose your information without your consent, in good faith, for the purposes of protecting our rights, protecting your safety or the safety of others, and disclosing for investigation of fraud or responding to governmental requests. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Security&lt;br/&gt; Xiaomi’s security measures&lt;br/&gt; We promise to keep your personal information safe. To prevent unauthorized access, disclosure or other similar risks, we have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and management processes to protect the information we collect from your mobile device. We will take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; For example, when you visit your Mi Account, you can choose our two-step verification process to ensure better security. When you send or receive information from Mi Home devices to our servers, we ensure that they are encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) and other algorithms. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; All of your personal information is stored on secure servers and protected in controlled facilities. We classify your data by importance and sensitivity and ensure that your personal information has the highest level of security. We guarantee that employees and third-party service providers who provide your products and services to you by accessing this information will have strict contractual confidentiality obligations and will be subject to disciplinary action or termination of cooperation if they fail to meet these obligations. In addition, we have specialized access controls for cloud-based data storage. All in all, we regularly review the practice of collecting, storing and processing information, including physical security measures to prevent any unauthorized access and use. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; We will take all practicable steps to protect your personal information. However, you should be aware that the use of the internet is not always safe and therefore we cannot guarantee the security or completeness of any personal information as it travels bidirectionally over the Internet. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; What you can do: &lt;br/&gt; • You can help protect the security of your personal information by not disclosing your login password or account information to anyone (unless they have been duly authorized by you). Whenever you log into Mi Home as the user of your Mi Account, you should always log out when the session ends, especially when you log in on someone else\'s computer or a public Internet terminal. &lt;br/&gt; • Xiaomi cannot be responsible for any security breach caused by third parties accessing your personal information due to your inability to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information. Notwithstanding the above, you must notify us immediately in the event of the unauthorized use of your account by any other user of the internet, or any other security breach. &lt;br/&gt; • Your assistance will help us protect the privacy of your personal information. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Retention policies&lt;br/&gt; We will retain your personal information for the purpose of collecting information if necessary, or to comply with applicable legal requirements or allowances. We will not retain personal information as long as we reasonably conclude that the retention of personal information does not achieve the purpose of collecting personal information and that we no longer need to retain said information for legal purposes, dispute resolution, the enforcement of our agreement, or other commercial purposes, or we will eliminate ways to associate the personal information with specific individuals. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Access other features on your device&lt;br/&gt; Our applications may have access to certain features on your device, such as enabling e-mail contacts, SMS storage, Wi-Fi network status, and more. This information is used to allow these applications to run on your device and to allow you to interact with them. At any time, you may revoke their license by closing the application at the device level or by contacting us at privacy@xiaomi.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; You can control your information! &lt;br/&gt; Control settings&lt;br/&gt; Xiaomi acknowledges that everyone\'s privacy concerns may vary. As a result, we provide some examples of the various ways Xiaomi offers you to choose from to limit the collection, use, disclosure, or processing of your personal information and to control your privacy settings: &lt;br/&gt; • Turn user experience planning and location access on or off; &lt;br/&gt; • Log into or out of your Mi Account; &lt;br/&gt; If you have previously granted us permission to use your personal information for the aforementioned reasons, you may change your decision at any time by contacting us in writing or by sending an e-mail to privacy@xiaomi.com. &lt;br/&gt; • You have the right to request access to and/or correction of any personal information we hold about you. When you update your personal information, you will be asked to verify your identity before we process your request. As soon as we have sufficient information to process your request to access or correct your personal information, we will respond to your request as long as applicable under the Data Protection Act. &lt;br/&gt; • We usually provide these services for free, but we reserve the right to charge a reasonable fee for data access requests. &lt;br/&gt; • If you would like to request access to personal data held by us or if you believe any information we hold about you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to us or e-mail us at the e-mail address provided. E-mail: privacy@xiaomi.com&lt;br/&gt; • For more details regarding the personal information in your Mi Home account, you can log into your account to access and change this information. &lt;br/&gt; Revoking consent&lt;br/&gt; • You may withdraw your consent to the collection, use, and/or disclosure of personal information held or controlled by us by sending an e-mail to privacy@xiaomi.com. We will process your request within a reasonable time after you have made your request and will not, at your request, collect, use, and/or disclose your personal information thereafter&lt;br/&gt; • Please note that the revocation of you consent may result in legal consequences. We will process the scope of your personal information which may, depending on your revocation, indicate that you cannot enjoy Mi Home products and services. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Transferring personal information outside the jurisdiction to which you belong&lt;br/&gt; If we need to transfer personal information outside your jurisdiction, whether it be to an affiliate (dealing with communications, social media, technology, or cloud services) or to a third-party service provider, we will apply all applicable laws. In particular, we will ensure that all such transfers meet the requirements of applicable local data protection laws by implementing the appropriate safeguards. Xiaomi may process or back up your personal information using overseas facilities operated and controlled by Mi Home. Currently, Xiaomi has data centers in Beijing, the United States, Singapore, and Germany. These overseas jurisdictions may or may not have data protection laws that are similar to the data protection laws of your jurisdiction. While we may transfer and store your personal information to our overseas facilities, this does not change our commitment to protect your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Other Provisions&lt;br/&gt; Minors&lt;br/&gt; • We consider it a parental responsibility to monitor children\'s use of our products and services. However, our policy does not require obtaining minors\' personal information or sending any promotional materials to such groups. &lt;br/&gt; • Xiaomi will not seek or attempt to seek to receive any personal information from minors. If a parent or guardian has reason to believe that minors submitted personal information to Mi Home without their prior consent, please contact us to ensure that such personal information is deleted and that any minor’s subscription to an applicable Mi Home service is cancelled. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Priority&lt;br/&gt; If you agree to the applicable user agreement and there is an inconsistency between said user agreement and this Privacy Policy, the user agreement will prevail. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Applicable laws&lt;br/&gt; [This Privacy Policy is governed by the law of Singapore.] We do not represent or guarantee that this Privacy Policy complies with the privacy laws of any jurisdiction and therefore you should not interpret the Privacy Policy in accordance with these laws. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Privacy Policy updates&lt;br/&gt; We conduct regular reviews of our privacy practices and we may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our information practices. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by e-mail (at the e-mail address specified in your account) or by posting on the Mi Home app or via mobile devices so that you can understand the information we collect and how we use them information. Such changes to the Privacy Policy will apply from the effective date provided by the notice or on the website. We encourage you to check this page regularly for the latest information on our privacy practices. Your continued use of our products and our services provided via the website, phone, and/or any other device will be deemed to be an updated Privacy Policy. We will obtain your consent again when we collect more personal information from you or if we wish to use or disclose your personal information for new purposes. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Do I have to agree to any third-party terms and conditions? &lt;br/&gt; Our Privacy Policy does not apply to products and services provided by third parties. Mi Home products and services may include third-party products and services, as well as links to third-party websites. Your information may also be collected when you use these products or services. Therefore, we strongly recommend that you take the time to read these third-party privacy policies just as you would read ours. We are not responsible for how third parties use the personal information they collect from you, nor do we control their use. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to other websites linked through our services. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; When you use these specific products, the following third-party terms and privacy policies apply: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; • When using the Google input method you must agree to the Google terms and conditions: &lt;a href=http://www.google.com/policies/privacy&gt;http://www.google.com/policies/privacy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt; • When using the SwiftKey input method you must agree to the SwiftKey terms and conditions: &lt;a href=http://swiftkey.com/en/privacy&gt;http://swiftkey.com/en/privacy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt; • When using the Fleksy input method you must agree to the Fleksy terms and conditions: &lt;a href=http://feedback.fleksy.com/tos&gt;http://feedback.fleksy.com/tos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Social media (features) and widgets&lt;br/&gt; Our website includes some social media features, including Facebook Like buttons, as well as widgets such as the Share button. These features may collect your IP address and the pages you visit on our website, and may set cookies for the proper functioning of the feature. Social media features and widgets may be hosted by third parties or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are subject to the Privacy Policy of the companies providing them. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Single sign-in&lt;br/&gt; Depending on the jurisdiction to which you belong, you may be able to log into our website using the login service provided by Facebook Connect or Open ID. These services will verify your identity and allow you to choose whether to share certain personal information with us, such as your name and e-mail address, to pre-populate our registration form. Services such as Facebook Connect allow you to choose whether or not to post your personal information on this site on your profile page to share with others online. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Contact us&lt;br/&gt; If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or if you have any questions about the collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information by Xiaomi, please contact our Data Protection Officer at the address below and mention Privacy Policy:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Xiaomi Singapore Pte Ltd&lt;br/&gt; #02-12, 20 Cross Street, China Square Central&lt;br/&gt; Singapore 048422&lt;br/&gt; E-mail: privacy@xiaomi.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Thank you for taking the time to familiarize yourself with our Privacy Policy! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</string>
    <string name="voice_not_support_internation">This feature isn\'t supported on global version of Mi Home app</string>
</resources>
